<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on JimmyLiao Notes</title><link>https://jimmyliao.net/tags/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on JimmyLiao Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 08:10:36 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jimmyliao.net/tags/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JimmyLiao.README (2022/05) - GoodBye InfuseAI</title><link>https://jimmyliao.net/post/2022-05-22-infuseai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 08:10:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jimmyliao.net/post/2022-05-22-infuseai/</guid><description>
&lt;p>This is the REAME as Customer Success Engineer at &lt;a href="https://www.infuseai.io/">InfuseAI&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I join InfuseAI as &lt;a href="https://jobs.infuseai.io/o/customer-success-engineer-taipei-city">Customer Success Engineer&lt;/a> after Appier AIQUA. As the first CSE at InfuseAI, I focus on Customer Experience and the Success Journey from scratch. Build up the communication and partnership with our SI partner from supporting existing and potential customer. Also work with support team to build up the support process to ease the developer's workload from the support/operation. With team, we build the related asset including: internal playbook, medium &lt;a href="https://jimmyliao.medium.com/setup-ssh-and-vscode-for-primehub-6628c0f4030c">posts&lt;/a>, troubleshootings, maintenance SOP, partner portal, showcase article and &lt;a href="https://github.com/InfuseAI/showcase">repo&lt;/a>, etc. I will write down how to build from scratch here later. :-)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://jimmyliao.net/images/2022/2022-05/2022-05-22-infuseai-01.jpg" alt="">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>5/17 is my last active working day at InfuseAI and will take weeks off, I would like to thanks your support in the past years. I do learn a lot from different area at here. Before I leave, I want to thank @clkao and @hlb, you provide me a good chance to see different point of view. Thanks for you all and I will try to take many positive memories to the next journey. Wish all of you best and success here. I hope we can keep in touch.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://jimmyliao.net/images/2022/2022-05/2022-05-22-infuseai-02.jpg" alt="">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Jimmy Liao.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>